(Sheldon:)You don't need him.
I'll represent you.
(Leonard:)- Hi.
- Hey. What brings you by?
(Penny:)Oh, had to go to a sales seminar
on our new sleeping pill.
(Bernadette:)Oh. How was it?
(Bernadette:)Great.
(Bernadette:)Fell asleep?
(Penny:)In, like, two minutes. Yeah.
(Penny:)So, how is everything
going around here?
(Penny:)Are you still upset about people
finding out you're pregnant?
(Bernadette:)I'm furious.
(Penny:)Sure, sure.
(Penny:)Uh, did you ever figure out
who told?
(Bernadette:)No. I confronted Barbara Chen,
but she claimed
(Bernadette:)she didn't know
what I was talking about.
(Penny:)Hmm. Well, I guess it's
just gonna remain a mystery,
(Penny:)you know, like whatever happened
in that seminar
(Penny:)after they dimmed the lights.
(Bernadette:)It had to be Barbara.
(Bernadette:)I've been trying to figure out
a way to get back at her.
(Howard:)Do you think
(Bernadette:)using her work computer
to Google
"how to be a prostitute"
is over the line?
(Penny:)Uh, you know, when I was
(Penny:)in high school, there was this girl
who was talking about me
(Penny:)behind my back, so me
and all my friends,
(Penny:)we cornered her in the bathroom
and forgave her.